

# CONTACT



Kyiv, Ukraine



borrline@gmail.com



git <a href="https://github.com/Yborline">https://github.com/Yborline</a>



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ yaroslav-borys-793268231/



+38(095)-602-53-85

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS/BEM
- JavaScript ES6+
- React.js
- WebPack. Parcel
- Handlebars
- **REST API**
- GitHub
- Figma
- NPM
- Redux
- Node.js
- **TypeScript**

## SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to work under pressure
- Conscientious
- Bussiness communication skills
- Responsible
- Creative
- Easy learner
- Honest
- Result-oriented
- Accurate
- Flexible

# LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian native
- Russian fluent
- English elementary

# YAROSLAV BORYS

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# SUMMARY

My new passion is creating and learning websites. That is why I am interested in the position of Front-End Developer. I have knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. During my studies, I worked on several projects (you can see my GitHub account). I am a fast learner and am ready for challenging tasks. I will be glad to become a part of big and interesting projects. My goal is to enjoy my work.

# PROJECT EXPERIENCE

WEB STUDIO (link to code) - [HTML, CSS, SASS, BEM], a website with a responsive layout

ICE CREAM (link to code) - [HTML, CSS, SASS, BEM, Parcel] (Team project/developer), a website a responsive layout.

FILMOTEKA (link to code) - [HTML, SASS, JS, API, AJAX, Parcel, Handlebars] (Team project/developer), application for choosing a movie.

PROJECT-BOOKS (link to code frontend or backend) -[HTML,CSS, JS, API, AJAX, Babel, React, NodeJS, Redux, Formik, Axios], application for book readers, which helps to control the assigned tasks.

REPAIR-MOBILE (link to code frontend or backend) -[HTML,CSS, JS, API, AJAX, Babel, React, NodeJS, Redux, Formik, Axios, Mui, dayjs, redux-persist], My personal project, which is still under development.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Sales manager

Mobile Trand | 2021 - 2022 |

Sales; fulfillment of the assigned tasks from the office; control over all changes in the company.

#### Head of warehouse

MK (Private company) 2018-2021

Organization of the work of the warehouse; analysis of orders and the formation of applications; even distribution of work among all employees. Reached the highest level of career growth in this company.

# **EDUCATION**

# State University of Infrastructure and Technologies

| 2018 - 2021 |

Faculty of transport technologies on railway transport

## Kyiv Professional College of Transport Infrastructure

| 2014 - 2018 |- with honours

Faculty of organization of transportation and management of railway transport

# ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

#### IT School GoIT

| 2021 - 2022 |

Full Stack Developer

## Children's Music School Nº14 them. D. Kabalevsky

| 2006 - 2014 |

Violin, piano